[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 12]
[Autopsy Room 1] [Morgue]
The deceased's family.
My son...
My son!
Heaven,
why can't you see?
If someone had to be taken,
i-it should've been me!
Why did you take my son?
Does it please you
to see the old
bury the young?
How is this even fair?
My son...
I offer you my condolences.
[Anatomy Room 2] [Postmortem Room 2]
What are you writing?
You won't let me see.
Parents burying their child...
What a tragedy.
Aren't you in town to investigate
Zhao Changyou?
What are you doing here?
During the investigation
of Zhao Changyou's social connections,
I found that he often
went to Shasha Hair Salon.
Before Li Dewu died,
he also just visited Shasha Hair Salon.
So I thought I'd come and see
if they were connected in any way.
Any findings?
Did they know each other?
Wang Ping said they both
got their hair washed at her place.
They were never together.
Nor did she see
they ever run into each other.
You really think they'd go there together?
Could it have happened—
two man at the same time?
Think about it.
One died shortly after the other did.
Both deaths happened at Yuhong Square.
The victims were both businessmen
with complicated social relations.
There are no ties between them
on the surface,
but it doesn't mean
there aren't any in private.
Go on.
I've reported to the superiors
that I'm joining
the investigation of the Li Dewu case.
Have you found anything?
On the night in question,
Li Dewu's parents never left home.
They have alibis, so they
can be ruled out as suspects.
Ruling out his own parents
as suspects—fairly reasonable.
What a brilliant judge you are.
After having dinner with them,
Chen Hong and her child
went back home at about 10:00.
Then she tucked her kid in.
Theoretically, she can also be ruled out
as a suspect.
What about the driver?
He said he waited all night
for Li Dewu to page him.
Though it never happened,
he still chose to stay at home.
Is it true?
About 80% true.
His neighbors can prove
that the car was parked downstairs
the whole time.
Around nine o'clock,
a kid even climbed onto the car.
So Wang Liye scolded him.
I'll ask again in a few days.
This needs to be 100% confirmed.
My son...
[Anatomy Room 2]
I can't bear to hear this.
A three.
A five!
A seven!
Pass. I'll pass.
Three of a kind plus one.
Bomb!
A pair of sevens.
A pair of eights.
A pair of jacks.
A pair of kings!
Is it a good time to play poker?
Don't you have work to do?
Go!
Get back to your work!
With the director gone,
who's going to pay us?
Yeah. Who's going to pay us?
Right. Who's going to pay us?
What to do with it?
Let me do it.
Let you do what?
You're just a woman.
What are you capable of?
Dad, have you forgotten?
I used to be an accountant in the factory.
If I hadn't married Dewu...
Just because you can keep the books,
does that mean you can manage a company?
You haven't seen much of the world.
Women are only competent
in the kitchen.
No, Dad. You have no idea.
Doing business nowadays
is different from before you retired.
These days, business is about going out,
begging for favors,
drinking heavily with others,
and networking.
You've gotten used to being a leader.
Is it appropriate for you
to swallow your pride
and beg for favors?
But I don't have a problem with it.
I'm up for this.
I have to get the company into good shape
so I can hand it over whole and intact
to your grandson in the future.
After all, he's only heir
of the Li family now.
Ms. Chen,
a brief introduction to you.
We're now in the warehouse.
-And this is...
-The shipping area.
Yes, exactly.
The main function here is to
transport oil in from outside.
Well, after Mr. Li's passing,
the workers have been
somewhat slacking off.
I know. It's okay.
You two enjoy whistling, right?
Come on, let's hear who whistles louder.
The winner stays.
The loser gets fired.
R-Really?
Alright. You whistle louder.
You get to stay.
And you are fired.
Thank you, Ms. Chen.
Off you go.
I...
You're Zhang, an accountant, right?
There is
a payment of 324,150 yuan
overdue by six months.
How come we haven't received it yet?
Whatever the reason,
I'll give you one more week.
Collect it in time,
or you'll be fired.
Leave the room. Go.
Alright.
Take her to HR to process her dismissal.
I...
Well, just go.
No, please, Mr. Chen.
Call me again if there's a similar event.
I have so much to learn from you.
Okay. Bye.
Why stare at me?
I'm just wondering
how you managed to become
completely different in just a few days.
Am I any different?
How so?
You're prettier. That's how.
So impressive.
So full of swagger.
Of course.
Drive.
Eyes on the road.
No, wait.
Dong, what is this about?
Are you serious?
Easy!
Let go of him.
What is this for?
"What is this for?"
When will you pay
the remaining 50,000?
What 50,000?
Don't play dumb with me.
I mean the 50,000 you owe me.
W-What?
Still putting on an act, huh?
I did the work for you,
yet you haven't paid in full.
No, you didn't finish the work.
The police said
that Li Dewu slipped on soybeans,
fell, and died.
Logically speaking,
you should refund me the previous 50,000.
That's crap.
Let me ask you.
Li Dewu died
in Yuhong Stadium, didn't he?
And I, Liang Zhendong,
rule Yuhong Stadium, don't I?
Yes.
That's it then.
You bidding was done
in my territory.
Shouldn't you pay up?
But I...
But what?
What's there to say?
You came to the nightclub that day.
My pals and the waiters here
all saw you, didn't they?
If one of them goes to the police
and blabs...
No, no.
Don't.
Dong, please.
Don't tell the police about it.
Why make a fuss at all?
Don't you just want that 50,000 yuan?
I'll definitely pay up.
Just give me a few days, okay?
I'm begging you.
Fine. I won't tell the police.
You get what I mean?
Okay, I'll pay you within three months.
Cut that crap!
I mean three days!
Three months?
I had a dream about Wu.
What did he say in it?
He asked what time it was.
What do you think that means?
Stop thinking about it.
Go to sleep.
He forgot his watch.
I need to burn it so it'll reach him.
That foolish broad.
She's never home.
Where did she place my son's watch?
Please say something.
Say what?
Is there a topic?
Didn't you suggest
that we leave Tiecheng together
for somewhere far away?
When did I ever suggest that?
Just two months ago. Don't you remember?
So you know it was two months ago.
Back then,
I was abused every day.
I asked you to take me away.
But what did you do?
You chickened out!
Now, Fatty Li is dead.
I'm in charge of the family's wealth
and the company.
Someone else is taking care of my child.
It hasn't been long
since my good days started,
and you're asking me to flee with you now?
You think I'm stupid or what?
Fine then.
We can stay here.
But you need to give me another 50,000.
You're literally asking me for money?
Calculate how many months
you have to work for 50,000!
The money is not for me.
It's for Dong.
Why him?
Previously, you had me ask him
to take Boss Wu out, didn't you?
He said 50,000 wasn't enough,
and demanded 100,000.
You seemed pretty eager to me,
so I told him yes.
Did I allow you to agree with it
on my behalf?
Then what should I have done?
Dad,
w-w-we didn't kill Dewu!
Despicable adulterers.
Dad, we really didn't...
You killed my son!
♪ Two tigers ♪
Dad, Dad!
Dewu just fell and died by accident, Dad!
♪ Two tigers ♪
I must kill you two bastards!
♪ Running fast ♪
It wasn't my idea!
It was hers.
She had me ask Dong for a favor!
How dare you shift the blame to me?
Listen up,
I didn't kill Li Dewu.
Even if I had, he would've deserved it!
Don't you know what a terrible son
you raised?
How did he treat me all those years?
Did he ever see me as a human?
I'm telling you,
he died, and it served him right!
Heaven did something right
by ridding the people of an evil!
You murdered your own husband.
I'm going to gouge your eyes out
and bury them with my son!
Everyone connected to you should die!
Don't do this!
Then the first one to die
will be your grandson!
You should be sewn in a cage and drowned!
Wang Liye, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Just wait till the police arrest you!
Quick. Go after him!
♪ How strange, strange, strange ♪
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ There will be war ♪
♪ There will be payback ♪
Hurry!
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ What is fated will come ♪
♪ What is not fated, don't force it ♪
♪ Think carefully ♪
♪ Wealth and glory are predestined ♪
Drive!
♪ Not the slightest bit
is up to human striving ♪
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ The wheel of fortune keeps turning ♪
What's the point
of wearing a seatbelt now?
♪ Sooner or later it will be our day ♪
♪ A piece of candy for you ♪
♪ I know you like radish and vegetables ♪
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ I know you like radish and vegetables ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
Catch up!
♪ I know you like radish and vegetables ♪
Yes, yes.
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
-Faster!
-Got it.
Get closer to him!
♪ Open the door ♪
It's too narrow in here.
♪ I know you like radish and vegetables ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
Make a turn!
Yes, yes.
♪ Two tigers are running fast ♪
♪ With their tails tucked
between their legs ♪
♪ For money and love ♪
Where has he gone?
♪ Being busy and deep in debt ♪
How did we lose him?
♪ How strange ♪
He's behind us. Quick!
♪ Two mice ♪
Follow up!
♪ Running fast ♪
Yes, I got it.
Quick!
♪ Two mice are running fast ♪
♪ Each of them has its own schemes ♪
♪ Harming themselves and others
for money ♪
♪ It only turns out to be another debt ♪
♪ How strange ♪
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ There will be war ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
Hit him!
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
Run him over!
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
No, I can't.
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ There will be war ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
Run him over
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
or we'll be the ones to die!
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ There will be payback ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
Charge!
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ Think carefully ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
[Stop]
♪ Don't be cocky ♪
♪ Be good, little bunny ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ Give me a piece of candy ♪
[Stop]
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ So I can see you in all your glory ♪
♪ How strange, strange, strange ♪
[No pedestrians allowed]
[Tiecheng Municipal Public Security
Bureau, Tieping District Division,]
[Daobei Police Station]
What should we do?